How old is Jason?
You stood against me. You chose your side. You
think you're free now. You think you can hide.
You think those
You just embarrass me You're a disgrace
You forgot who holds the strings You forgot who
pays the bills You think you have a voice, my boy
I'll show you what control still builds You are
an adult Let's see how long you last The line is
dead, the signal's gone I've got the cord, it
won't be long Till you come crawling back to me
How will you talk, boy, when you're not free?
You must talk, boy, when you're not free No
service, no connection Just me
You're just a child. You're weak and you're
slow. You can't survive out there. You have
nowhere to go. They'll get tired of you. They'll
see the burden. And when they throw you out, I'll
be the one to let you in. Click. The line is dead.
The signal's gone. I've cut the cord. It won't be
long till you come crawling back to me. How will
you talk, boy, when you're not free?
Your call cannot be completed as dialed Please
hang up and try again, but there's no one to call
You're all alone, Aubrey.
You're all alone.
The line
is dead, the signal's gone It's cut the cord, it
won't be long Till you come crawling back to me
How will you talk, boy, when you're not free?
Just maybe.
No service. No service.